Guide to the Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation records
1950-2006
1986-2006
YCAL MSS 342
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
109
(87 boxes)
The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Records document the activities of the foundation during its nearly two-decade existence, including the administration and distribution of Georgia O'Keeffe's physical and financial assets, the management of her intellectual property rights, and the publication of a catalogue raisonné of her work, among other accomplishments. The records cover the foundation's relationships with a variety of museums, galleries, collectors, publishers, and exhibition organizers, as well as with art historians, artists, authors, biographers, conservators, photographers, and the general public, and with its own financial and legal advisors. Also included in Series I are photocopied sets of letters to O'Keeffe from her friends Mangus (Mike) Harding, Ruth Carter Johnson, and Caroline Keck.
Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation, 2009.
Conditions Governing Access
Series I, Correspondence Files, is open for research.
Series II, Board of Directors Files, is restricted until March 4, 2019.
Series III, Financial Files, is restricted until March 4, 2029.
Associated Materials
Most of the material related to the estate of Georgia O'Keeffe is held in Alfred Stieglitz/Georgia O'Keeffe Archive Addition (YCAL MSS 345).
Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation
The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation, a self-limiting nonprofit organization, was established in May 1989 with the purpose of expanding and perpetuating the artistic legacy of the artist Georgia O'Keeffe (1887-1986) for the public benefit. The foundation's defined term limit was twenty years from the receipt of O'Keeffe's assets, or 2006. Its mission included the documentation of O'Keeffe's work, the distribution of her assets, including more than one thousand paintings, drawings, and photographs, and the transition of her home and studio in Abiquiu, New Mexico, from a private residence to an historic house museum.
The foundation's Board of Directors consisted of five members, three of whom, as co-representatives of the artist's estate, were permanent appointments: O'Keeffe's grand-nephew Raymond R. Krueger, her niece June O'Keeffe Sebring, and her assistant Juan Hamilton. The first two elected directors were the art historians Richard R. Brettell and Charles C. Eldredge, who served from 1989-1995. Other pairs of directors elected over time were Vincent A. Carrozza and Bill Katz (1996-1998) and Anne d'Harnoncourt and Earl A. Powell III (1999-2006). The foundation's first (provisional) president was Santa Fe attorney Robert P. Worcester (1989-1990), followed by Elizabeth Glassman (1990-1998); Worcester was reappointed as president of the foundation in 1999. Agapita ("Pita") Judy Lopez was a director of the foundation from 1999-2006; she had worked for O'Keeffe during the last ten years of the artist's life, and was afterward employed by her estate. Lopez served as secretary/treasurer of the foundation from 1989-1996, and as assistant director from 1996-1999. The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation was headquartered in Abiquiu, and maintained a second office in Santa Fe from 1991-2002.
Distribution of the art in O'Keeffe's estate began with fifty-four works placed with eight museums with which she had had long-standing relationships: the Art Institute of Chicago; Brooklyn Museum; Cleveland Museum of Art; Metropolitan Museum of Art; Museum of Fine Arts, Boston; Museum of Modern Art; National Gallery of Art; and the Philadelphia Museum of Art. In 1992 the foundation expanded the program to include gifts to a wider range of museums, galleries, and historical societies around the country and the world, as well as to the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum (founded in Santa Fe in 1995). O'Keeffe's collection of Alfred Stieglitz photographs and photogravures was distributed to museums as well.
Expanding and perpetuating O'Keeffe's artistic legacy also took the form of promoting the exhibition of her work. The foundation oversaw the completion of the centennial show Georgia O'Keeffe, 1887-1986 (1987-1989; traveled from the National Gallery to three American museums, accompanied by the publication Georgia O'Keeffe, Art and Letters ), and was instrumental in the organization of two important exhibits: the artist's first international retrospective, Georgia O'Keeffe: American and Modern (1993-1994; administered by InterCultura and the United States Information Agency) and The Book Room: Georgia O'Keeffe's Library in Abiquiu (1997; organized with the Grolier Club, New York, and also shown in Santa Fe). Foundation staff members were closely involved in three major traveling exhibitions organized by museums, O'Keeffe on Paper (2000), O'Keeffe's O'Keeffes: the Artist's Collection (2001-2002), and Georgia O'Keeffe: Color and Conservation (2006), and regularly sent loans from the foundation's collection to various American and international projects. The foundation's most substantial effort regarding the artist's legacy, however, was the two-volume Georgia O'Keeffe: Catalogue Raisonné, which it published in 1999 with the National Gallery of Art and Yale University Press.
Other initiatives focused on the commemoration of Georgia O'Keeffe's life. Since 1989 the foundation had undertaken measures to preserve and maintain the home she had purchased in Abiquiu in 1945, as well as its contents and gardens, while offering limited public tours of the property. In 1996 the foundation implemented a Historic American Buildings Survey (HABS), then oversaw the O'Keeffe Home and Studio's designation as a National Historic Landmark in 1998 and its inclusion on the National Register of Historic Places. An oral history project was begun in 1999, with the goal of recording and transcribing interviews with O'Keeffe's surviving relatives, colleagues, friends, and employees. And in 1995 the foundation worked closely with the United States Postal Service to create the Georgia O'Keeffe commemorative postage stamp issued in Santa Fe on May 23, 1996.
A great part of the foundation's work was stewardship over the copyright of all of O'Keeffe's paintings, drawings, sculptures, and writings, and staff members were vigilant in granting, denying, and policing all public and private attempts to reproduce O'Keeffe images in any format, regardless of who owned the artwork or literary papers. The foundation worked with the Artists Rights Society (ARS) to help monitor and coordinate intellectual property rights and to collect reproduction fees, which produced a significant income stream. In addition to all of the above projects, the foundation donated funds to a number of community organizations and charities, mostly local schools, churches, and groups to which O'Keeffe had made contributions during her lifetime.
The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation transferred its residual assets, including the remainder of O'Keeffe's artwork, her book collection, some research papers and archival materials, and the Abiquiu home and studio, to the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum in 2006. The foundation transferred its records and Georgia O'Keeffe's financial, legal, and medical papers to the Beinecke Library in 2009; the latter group of material comprises the Alfred Stieglitz/Georgia O'Keeffe Archive Addition (YCAL MSS 345).
Scope and Contents
The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Records consist of correspondence and administrative papers, board of directors' minutes, and financial records of the organization. They document the actions of the foundation's board of directors and the day-to-day activities of the administrative staff as they built relationships with museums, collectors, publishers, and the interested public over two decades. The papers date from the death of the artist in 1986 through the foundation's termination in 2006, with one exception as noted in the folder list (box 42) below. Among the activities covered are the formation of the foundation's plans and principles, the management and dispersal of O'Keeffe's artworks and financial assets, the administration and protection of her intellectual property rights, the organization and implementation of the O'Keeffe catalogue raisonné, and the supervision of tours of O'Keeffe's home and studio in Abiquiu. Documenting the founding and lifespan of one of the country's earliest "artist's foundations," the records will be of interest to anyone researching the history of that branch of philanthropy, or of Georgia O'Keeffe and her legacy.
The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Records does not contain original artwork, original correspondence to or by O'Keeffe, exhibition catalogues or the O'Keeffe catalogue raisonné, oral history interview recordings or transcripts, or HABS drawings of the Abiquiu property. Series I holds photocopies of letters to O'Keeffe (in the folders for Mangus Harding, Ruth Carter Johnson, Caroline Keck, and "O'Keeffe letters" in the Abiquiu Office Files subseries; see notes in the folder list below) and a photocopy of an Alfred Stieglitz letter (in the folder "Peter Bunnell" in the Santa Fe Office Files subseries). Most of the records pertaining to the settlement of the artist's estate are held in the Alfred Stieglitz/Georgia O'Keeffe Archive Addition (YCAL MSS 345).
Arrangement
Organized into three series: I. Correspondence Files, circa 1950-2006. Series II. Board of Directors Files, 1989-2006. III. Financial Files, 1969-2006.
Art -- Exhibitions; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations -- New Mexico; Endowments -- New Mexico; Library exhibits; Financial records; Brettell, Richard R., 1949-; Carrozza, Vincent P.; D'Harnoncourt, Anne, 1943-2008; Drohojowska-Philp, Hunter, 1952-; Eldredge, Charles C., 1944-; Gallup, Donald, 1913-2000; Glassman, Elizabeth; Hamilton, Juan, 1945-; Harding, Magnus Swenson, 1921-1993; Keck, Caroline K. (Caroline Kohn); Krueger, Raymond R.; Landau, Emily Fisher; Lynes, Barbara Buhler, 1942-; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 -- Catalogues raisonnés; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 -- Exhibitions; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 -- Homes and haunts -- New Mexico -- Abiquiu; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 -- Library -- Catalogs; Peters, Sarah Whitaker; Powell, Earl A.; Reily, Nancy Hopkins, 1934-; Rose, Barbara, 1938-; Sebring, June O'Keeffe; Varon, Malcolm; Artists Rights Society; Grolier Club; Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation; Georgia O'Keeffe Museum; InterCultura of Fort Worth; J. Paul Getty Museum; Kemper Museum of Contemporary Art; Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, N.Y.); Los Angeles County Museum of Art; Milwaukee Art Museum; Museum of Fine Arts (Museum of New Mexico); National Gallery of Art (U.S.); National Trust for Historic Preservation in the United States; Philadelphia Museum of Art; Santa Fe Chamber Music Festival; Whitney Museum of American Art
- Correspondence Files, circa 1950-2006; Series I; 65; (52 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Series I is organized into four subseries: Abiquiu Office Files; Santa Fe Office Files; Catalogue Raisonné Project; O'Keeffe House Tour Records
  Scope and Contents
  The series contains both correspondence and subject files which were created, titled, and arranged by the foundation staff. The first subseries primarily contains material related to the management of Georgia O'Keeffe's artwork and images of it, covering its distribution, exhibition, and intellectual property rights, but also includes other general administrative records. The Santa Fe Office Files hold Elizabeth Glassman's office records, the content of which mirror much of what is in the preceding subseries. The subseries Catalogue Raisonné Project contains correspondence, reports, and other records documenting the foundation's publication Georgia O'Keeffe: Catalogue Raisonné (1999); topics include issues of personnel, the advisory committee, authentication, conservation, finances, photography, and research. The last subseries, O'Keeffe House Tour Records, contains letters requesting tours, prepayments, schedules, docent records, visitor thank-you letters, and visitor surveys.
  - Abiquiu Office Files
    Arranged under five headings: Museums, exhibition organizers, and commercial galleries; Individuals, organizations, and subjects; Applicants for foundation president; Chronological files; and Faxes to and from Santa Fe office.
    - Museums, exhibition organizers, and commercial galleries
      - Ackland Art Museum (Box 1)
      - Addison Gallery of American Art (Box 1)
      - Adirondack Museum (Box 1)
      - Albuquerque Museum (Box 1)
      - Amarillo Art Center (Box 1)
      - American-Australian Foundation for the Arts (Box 1)
      - Amon Carter Museum of Western Art, 3 (Box 1)
      - Amherst College (Box 1)
      - Arkansas Art Center (Box 1)
      - Art Gallery of Ontario (Box 1)
      - Art Institute of Chicago (Box 1)
      - Barnes Foundation (Box 1)
      - Birmingham Museum of Art (Box 1)
      - Bowdoin College. Museum of Art (Box 1)
      - Brooklyn Museum (Box 1)
      - Bruce Museum of Arts and Science (Box 1)
      - Buffalo Bill Historical Center (Box 1)
      - California College of Arts and Crafts (Box 1)
      - Carone Gallery (Box 1)
      - Centre Georges Pompidou (Box 1)
      - Chrysler Museum of Art (Box 1)
      - Cincinnati Art Museum (Box 1)
      - Cleveland Museum of Art, 2 (Box 1)
      - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 2 (Box 1)
      - Columbus Museum of Art, 2 (Box 1)
      - Corcoran Museum of Art (Box 1)
      - Cranbrook Academy of Art. Museum (Box 1)
      - Dallas Museum of Art, 4 (Box 1)
      - Daniel Wolf, Inc. (Box 1)
      - Dayton Art Institute (Box 1)
      - Denver Art Museum (Box 1)
      - Des Moines Art Center (Box 1)
      - Eiteljorg Museum (Box 1)
      - Elvehjem Museum of Art (Box 1)
      - Fine Arts Museum of San Francisco (Box 1)
      - Fisk University, 2 (Box 1)
      - Fort Wayne Museum of Art, 2 (Box 1)
      - Fundación Juan March, 2 (Box 1)
      - Frederick R. Weisman Art Museum (Box 1)
      - George Eastman House (Box 2)
      - Georgia Museum of Art, 2 (Box 2)
      - Georgia O'Keeffe Museum, 11 (Box 2)
      - Georgia O'Keeffe Museum, 3 (Box 3)
      - Gerald Peters Gallery (Box 3)
      - Grolier Club, 26 (Box 3)
      - Grolier Club (Box 4)
        General note
        Box contains exhibition labels and printout from bibliographic database
      - Harvard University (Box 5)
      - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art (Box 5)
      - High Museum of Art (Box 5)
      - Hirschl & Adler Galleries (Box 5)
      - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden (Box 5)
      - Honolulu Academy of Arts, 2 (Box 5)
      - Indiana University Art Museum (Box 5)
      - Indianapolis Museum of Art (Box 5)
      - InterCultura of Fort Worth, 10 (Box 5)
      - InterCultura, 22 (Box 6)
      - International Arts, 5 (Box 7)
      - J. Paul Getty Museum, 6 (Box 7)
      - Janie C. Lee Gallery (Box 7)
      - Jewish Museum (Box 7)
      - John Berggruen Gallery (Box 7)
      - Joslyn Museum (Box 7)
      - Kansas City Art Institute (Box 7)
      - Katonah Museum of Art (Box 7)
      - Kemper Museum of Contemporary Art (Box 7)
      - Kunsthaus Zürich, 2 (Box 7)
      - Laurence Miller Gallery (Box 7)
      - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 5 (Box 7)
      - Lowe Art Museum (Box 8)
      - Louisiana Museum of Modern Art (Box 8)
      - Madison Art Center (Box 8)
      - Masterworks Foundation (Box 8)
      - Memphis Brooks Museum of Art (Box 8)
      - McNay Art Museum (Box 8)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 3 (Box 8)
      - M. H. De Young Memorial Museum, 2 (Box 8)
      - Michael Lord Gallery (Box 8)
      - Miami Art Museum (Box 8)
      - Millicent Rogers Museum (Box 8)
      - Milwaukee Art Museum, 5 (Box 8)
      - Minneapolis Institute of Art, 2 (Box 8)
      - Mississippi Museum of Art, 4 (Box 8)
      - Montclair Art Museum (Box 9)
      - Montgomery Museum of Fine Arts (Box 9)
      - Museo Nacional Centro de Arte Reina Sofiá (Box 9)
      - Museo Rufino Tamayo, 2 (Box 9)
      - Museum of Contemporary Art/Denver (Box 9)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 2 (Box 9)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 2 (Box 9)
      - Museum of Fine Arts (Museum of New Mexico), 5 (Box 9)
      - Museum of Fine Arts (Saint Petersburg, Fla.), 2 (Box 9)
      - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.), 2 (Box 9)
      - Museum of the Southwest (Midland, Tex.) (Box 9)
      - Museum of Western Art (Denver, Colo.) (Box 9)
      - National Gallery of Art (U.S.), 11 (Box 10)
      - National Gallery of Canada (Box 11)
      - National Museum of American Art (Box 11)
      - National Museum of Modern Art, Tokyo, 2 (Box 11)
      - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 2 (Box 11)
      - National Galleries of Scotland (Box 11)
      - National Portrait Gallery (Smithsonian Institution) (Box 11)
      - Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art, 2 (Box 11)
      - New Jersey State Museum (Box 11)
      - New York Public Library (Box 11)
      - Norman Rockwell Museum (Box 11)
      - Northeastern University (Box 11)
      - Norton Museum of Art (Box 11)
      - Oglethorpe University Museum (Box 11)
      - Oregon Art Institute, 2 (Box 11)
      - Pace/MacGill, 2 (Box 11)
      - Panhandle-Plains Historical Museum (Box 11)
      - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (Box 11)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 4 (Box 11)
      - Phillips Collection, 3 (Box 11)
      - Phoenix Art Museum, 4 (Box 11)
      - Princeton University Art Museum (Box 11)
      - Rahr-West Museum, 2 (Box 12)
      - Reed College (Box 12)
      - Reynolda House, 3 (Box 12)
      - Richard York Gallery (Box 12)
      - Robert Miller Gallery, Inc. (Box 12)
      - Rosenbach Museum & Library (Box 12)
      - Roswell Museum and Art Center, 2 (Box 12)
      - Royal Academy of Arts (Box 12)
      - St. Louis Art Museum (Box 12)
      - Salander-O'Reilly Galleries (Box 12)
      - San Antonio Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - San Diego Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art (Box 12)
      - San Jose Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - Santa Barbara Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - Seattle Art Museum (Box 12)
      - Sheldon Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - Smithsonian Institution (Box 12)
      - Spencer Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - Staatliche Kunsthalle Baden-Baden (Box 12)
      - Stanford University. Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - Sun Prairie Historical Library and Museum (Box 12)
      - Tate Gallery (Box 12)
      - Tel Aviv Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - Terra Museum of American Art (Box 12)
      - Tokyo Metropolitan Museum of Photography, 2 (Box 12)
      - University of Arizona. Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - University of Arizona. Center for Creative Photography (Box 12)
      - University of Chicago (Box 12)
      - University of Minnesota. University Art Museum (Box 12)
      - University of New Mexico (Box 12)
      - University of Oklahoma. Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - University of Southern Maine (Box 12)
      - Valparaiso University. Museum of Art (Box 12)
      - Vatican Museum (Box 12)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 12)
      - Wadsworth Atheneum, 2 (Box 12)
      - Wake Forest University (Box 12)
      - Walker Art Center (Box 12)
      - Washburn Gallery (Box 12)
      - Weatherspoon Art Museum (Box 12)
      - Weston Gallery (Box 12)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, 4 (Box 12)
      - Wichita Art Museum (Box 12)
      - Williams College, Museum of Art, 2 (Box 12)
      - Worcester Art Museum, 2 (Box 12)
      - Yale University. Art Gallery (Box 12)
      - Yokohama Museum of Art (Box 12)
    - Individuals, organizations, and subjects
      - Abbeville Press (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu Elementary School (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu house access (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu Land Grant (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu Library (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu Mutual Domestic Water Consumers Association (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu Realty (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu Reservoir (Box 13)
      - Abiquiu town meetings (Box 13)
      - Acequi del Pueblo de Abiquiu (Box 13)
      - Achenbach Foundation for Graphic Arts (Box 13)
      - Adams, Mary (Box 13)
      - Adato, Perry Miller (Box 13)
      - Agee, William (Box 13)
      - Albuquerque Public Schools (Box 13)
      - Alexander, Jane (Box 13)
      - Alvin Cooperman Productions, Inc. (Box 13)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 13)
      - American Association of Museums, 3 (Box 13)
      - American Association for State and Local History (Box 13)
      - American Federation of Arts (Box 13)
      - Annual report (Box 13)
      - Angelitos de Abiquiu (Box 13)
      - Architectural Digest, 2 (Box 13)
      - Archuleta authentication (Box 13)
      - Archuleta, Fidel (Box 13)
      - Archuleta, Gerald (Box 13)
      - A.R.T. Co. (Box 13)
      - Art Dealers Association of America (Box 13)
      - Art in Embassies Program, 2 (Box 13)
      - Art Law (Box 13)
      - Art, miscellaneous (Box 13)
      - Artists Rights Society, 3 (Box 13)
      - Artwork on loan and request (Box 13)
      - Asia Sale - Taiwan and Japan (Box 13)
      - Associated Press (Box 13)
      - Association of Histories in American Art (Box 13)
      - Attorney General of New Mexico (Box 13)
      - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Collection of American Literature (Box 13)
      - Benedikt Taschen Verlag, 2 (Box 13)
      - Benson, Cynda (Box 13)
      - Berry, Elizabeth (Box 13)
      - Bochner, Jay (Box 13)
      - Bode, Karl (Box 13)
      - Bonet, Llorenç (Box 14)
      - Book sales (Box 14)
      - Bookroom research by Georgia O'Keeffe Museum scholars, 2 (Box 14)
      - Brady, Kerry (Box 14)
      - British Broadcasting Corporation, 2 (Box 14)
      - Brompton Books Corporation (Box 14)
      - Brown & Wood (Box 14)
      - Brown Foundation (Box 14)
      - Bry, Doris, 2 (Box 14)
      - Budnick, Dan (Box 14)
      - Burnett Foundation (Box 14)
      - Calder pin logo (Box 14)
      - Calendars, 2 (Box 14)
      - Callaway Editions, Inc., 9 (Box 14)
      - Canones Early Childhood Center (Box 14)
      - Caponigro, Eleanor (Box 14)
      - Carpenter, Laura (Box 14)
      - CD-ROM, 2 (Box 14)
      - Cedco Publishing Company, 3 (Box 14)
      - Censorship (Box 14)
      - Century Bank (Box 14)
      - Chatham Hall (Box 14)
      - Chave, Anna C. (Box 14)
      - Christie's, 3 (Box 14)
      - Christmas cards, 2 (Box 15)
      - Clift, William (Box 15)
      - Coe, Ted (Box 15)
      - College of Santa Fe (Box 15)
      - College Arts Association (Box 15)
      - Collins, Jane Downer (Box 15)
      - Comgraphix (Box 15)
      - Commercial reproduction (Box 15)
      - Continuum Productions (Box 15)
      - Corn, Wanda M. (Box 15)
      - Courier information (Box 15)
      - Cross, Villere J. (Box 15)
      - Creative Products of America (Box 15)
      - Cutler, Margo (Box 15)
      - Dar al Islam (Box 15)
      - Decker, Andrew (Box 15)
      - Delaney, Beauford (Box 15)
      - Dietrich Foundation (Box 15)
      - Domenici, Pete (Box 15)
      - Downey, James (Box 15)
      - Drohojowska-Philp, Hunter, 3 (Box 15)
      - Dumke Foundation (Box 15)
      - Duryea, Polly (Box 15)
      - Ebsworth, Barney A. (Box 15)
      - Education reports (Box 15)
      - Eisler, Benita (Box 15)
      - Eldredge, Charles C. (Box 15)
      - Ewing, Virginia Hunter (Box 15)
      - Ferran, Leonard (Box 15)
      - Fineberg, Jonathan David (Box 15)
      - Fishel, Edith (Box 15)
      - Flores, Dan L. (Box 15)
      - Foundation Center (Box 15)
      - Foundations for Grant Applications (Box 15)
      - Frankenthaler, Helen (Box 15)
      - Frazier, Nancy (Box 15)
      - "Friends" group (Box 15)
      - Friess, Constance (Box 15)
      - Fund-raising (Box 15)
      - Gág, Wanda (Box 15)
      - Galison Books (Box 15)
      - Gallup, Donald Clifford, 2 (Box 15)